sharewise.com 2015-09-30

# Welcome to the new sharewise

Print  | 

As of July 08, 2015 

This Privacy Policy applies to all of the services offered on sites owned and operated by us (the “Services”). When we refer to ‘’we’’ or ‘’our’’, we are referring to sharewise GmbH. 

###  1\. Fundamental Principles of Privacy Policy 

In the operation of our business, we may collect Personal Information about you, and we recognize and respect the privacy rights with regard to, and the importance of protecting, such information. To show our deepest commitment and responsibility to safeguard your Personal Information, we have established this Privacy Policy. 

Our management and employees are expected to strictly observe all regulatory, legal and corporate requirements for handling and protecting Personal Information. We have also established internal safety standards, accountability protocols and procedures, and preventive measures to protect against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of Personal Information. 

As part of our continuous efforts to monitor and ensure the safety of your Personal Information, we regularly review our personal information management system, including compliance by our management and employees with this Privacy Policy. 

###  2\. Personal Information 

"Personal Information" shall mean information relating to an individual who is or can be identified from such information. Personal Information includes name, date of birth, gender, address, e-mail address, credit card number and expiration date, bank account details, and other information that can be used to identify a specific individual. We may collect Personal Information from you when you sign up for and use our Services, place an order with us, contact us by mail, phone or email, make a written complaint or request, and/or participate in our surveys or questionnaires. Also, when you visit our websites, our web servers automatically collect the IP address assigned to you by your internet service provider, the website from which you visit us, which of our websites you visit, and the date and length of your visit. 

###  3\. Proper Acquisition 

We acquire Personal Information only by proper and lawful means and not through deception or any other wrongful means. When Personal Information is provided to us by third parties, we take appropriate steps to verify that such information is reliable and obtained in a proper manner. 

When you register via your social media account the concerned social media provider will automatically provide to us your personal account data such as your name, social media account ID, email, workplace, gender or further account-related data or profile pictures. Please note that not all of the provided data is stored to our data bases (e.g. no information regarding workplace, gender or profile pictures). However, in such case you are using a third party service which is independent of us and whose data processing procedures we are unable to influence. Please find further information on data protection at the websites of the relevant third party service providers. 

###  4\. Use of Personal Information 

We use Personal Information only for the following purposes: 

  1. To provide our Services and information regarding our products;
  2. For your proper registration as a user and personal verification;
  3. For transaction of everyday business with our customers and business partners;
  4. To tailor our Services for individual customers, such as by providing personalized content, offers or promotions;
  5. To perform analysis and conduct market research for developing and improving our Services in full compliance with applicable data protection laws;
  6. In connection with an investigation of suspected or actual fraudulent or illegal activity such as insider trading; and
  7. To comply with contractual, regulatory and legal requirements.

###  5\. Transfer of Personal Information to Third Parties 

Except as permitted by applicable data protection laws, we will not, without your prior consent, provide or disclose your Personal Information to third parties except in the following circumstances: 

  1. To comply with any applicable law, regulation, or governmental request;
  2. To protect against immediate harm to personal safety or property, and procuring prior consent from the individual concerned is difficult;
  3. For public health reasons, protection of children’s privacy and other public interest concerns, and procuring prior consent from the individual concerned is difficult;
  4. To provide necessary cooperation to relevant national and local governmental authorities, and procuring prior consent from the individual concerned hampers or jeopardizes such cooperation efforts;
  5. For outsourcing to third party service providers in connection with the performance of certain services on our behalf, such as direct mailing and phone calls, through contractual and written agreements requiring adherence by such third parties to confidentiality and privacy terms;
  6. For outsourcing to processors of payment transactions and provider of related services in connection with your payment transactions, through contractual and written agreements requiring adherence by such third parties to confidentiality and privacy terms.

###  6\. Third Party Service Provider 

When we share or disclose your Personal Information with third party service providers for processing or handling Personal Information for us, we conduct thorough investigation to verify the reliability and trustworthiness of such service providers, and take necessary measures to ensure their compliance with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

###  7\. Cookies and other Technologies 

1\. We may store certain information in the form of “cookies” on your PC so that we can optimize our web pages to suit your preferences. Cookies are small text files stored and saved on your computer by your Internet browser. You may refuse the acceptance of cookies, by selecting the relevant settings in your Internet browser. In providing our Services, we have further contractual arrangements with multiple online partners. We also have arrangements with marketing firms to use automated means such as web beacons and tracking technologies such as cookies to collect information. 

2\. Information collected through the use of technologies such as web beacons and cookies may include IP address, domain name and referring URLs. Such information is used for research purposes to better understand your activities and preferences, and to evaluate the quality of our Services. Information collected by such technologies cannot be used to identify individual users and will not result in an invasion of your privacy rights. We will obtain records of usage of our Services from the marketing firms, and the storage and handling of such records are managed by us. 

3\. We use advertising service providers (Google Inc. and so on, the “Advertisers”), to place some of our advertisements for our Services on their sites. Advertisements placed by Advertisers may use tracking technologies that allow collection of certain information. Such information is not provided or disclosed to us, and is handled and managed by Advertisers in accordance with their privacy policies. Please note that such services are provided by third companies which are independent of us and whose data processing procedures we are unable to influence. Please visit Advertisers’ sites for further information. 

4\. We use the services of Geniee, Inc. and their tracking technologies to collect certain information. Please note that such service is provided by Geniee, Inc. as a third company which is independent of us and whose data processing procedures we are unable to influence. For further information about the use of their tracking technologies, the types of information collected, and ways to disable such tracking technologies, please visit the privacy policies of the respective service providers. 

5\. This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. In case that the IP anonymization on this website has been activated Google will shorten the IP address within the European Union or other contractual states of the treaty of the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases will the IP address be transferred to the United States and will be shortened there. On behalf of the operator of this website Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google will not associate the IP address transmitted by your browser when using Google Analytics with any other data held by Google. 

You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. Furthermore you can prevent Google’s collection and use of data (cookies and IP address) by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available under 

<https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en-GB>

You may also prevent data collection by Google Analytics by clicking on the link below. This will set an opt-out cookie preventing any future collection of your data when you visit this website: 

Click here to opt out of Google Analytics 

On this website, Google Analytics has been supplemented with the “anonymizeIp” code so as to ensure the above described anonymized collection of IP addresses (“IP masking”). 

You may obtain further information, including on conditions of use and data protection with Google Analytics, at http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/gb.html and https://www.google.com/intl/gb/policies/ or the respective language versions of these websites. 

###  8\. Access Your Personal Information 

You may review or make any corrections to your Personal Information at any time by accessing your account information, or by contacting us. We will take timely, reasonable and appropriate measures to comply with your request. However, accessing or disclosing Personal Information may be limited in some circumstances such as potential harm to personal safety or property, severe disruption to our regular business, and illegal activities. 

###  9\. Revision 

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time as necessary. Upon revision, the latest version of the Privacy Policy will be up-loaded to our website. 

Print  |
